{"data":[{"question":"Nine state attorney generals have been meeting lately, apparently to prepare a tobacco-company-style humdinger court case against softies.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"attorney generals ","b":"have been meeting","c":"lately","d":"apparently ","answer":"1","explain":"- Attorney generals-> attorneys general","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"When seeing near the horizon, the moon appears strikingly larger than when viewed overhead.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"seeing ","b":"near ","c":"strikingly ","d":"overhead","answer":"1","explain":"- Seeing -> seen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The firemen were unable to determine exactly what caused the fire, when they said that they would continue the investigation.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to determine ","b":"what ","c":"when ","d":"would continue ","answer":"3","explain":"- When-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Because of its strong record during earlier recessions, the mutual fund has and will continue to be attractive to small investors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because of ","b":"its ","c":"has and will ","d":"attractive to ","answer":"3","explain":"- Has and will-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Both china, Russia, and the united states are aware of the role they play in world affairs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Both china","b":"are ","c":"aware ","d":"they ","answer":"1","explain":"- Both China-> China","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither Russia nor the United States have been able to discover a mutually satisfactory plan for gradual disarmament.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"nor ","b":"have been able ","c":"a mutually ","d":"satisfactory plan ","answer":"2","explain":"- Have been-> has been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"An echo is a sound heard subsequently it is reflected from an object.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"heard ","b":"subsequently ","c":"reflected from ","d":"an object","answer":"2","explain":"- Subsequently-> as if","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"While the two reappeared after being absent for over a month, everyone in the expedition was surprised to find them so little changed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While ","b":"being ","c":"for over ","d":"so little ","answer":"1","explain":"- While-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"We had been in the city not more than two days until we found that we needed a guide.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had been in ","b":"not more than ","c":"until ","d":"needed ","answer":"3","explain":"- Until-> not until","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"A measuring worm can hold itself straight out from a branch so that looks like a small twig.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can hold","b":"itself","c":"out ","d":"so that looks ","answer":"4","explain":"- So that-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}